nice to meet you.
初めまして
It's so cute.
めちゃめちゃ可愛いですね
Could it be that?
もしかしてあれですか?
Are you in the entertainment industry?
芸能関係の方ですか?
Actress?
女優さん?
That's not the case.
そんなことないです
Aren't you interested in that?
そう いうの興味ないの?
No.
ないです
By the way, do you like flowers?
ちなみに花は好き?
Is it a flower?
花ですか?
I like it.
好きです
What do you like?
何が好き?
flower?
花?
Zurich.
チューリック
cute.
可愛い
It kind of looks like Zurich.
なんか チューリックっぽい
It suits you.
似合う
Look behind me.
後ろに見て
There are a lot of flowers, right?
いっぱい花あるでしょ
Which flower do you like?
この花、どれが好き?
I like this.
これが好きです
I like it, the mood is good.
いいね、ノリが
TRUE?
本当?
Isn't it early?
早くないですか?
It's unsightly.
人目悪い
marriage.
結婚
It has now been decided.
今の決まったんですよね
More beautiful than flowers.
花よりも綺麗
It's early.
早いですよ
It's a speed controller.
スピードコンです
It's really fast.
めちゃくちゃ早いですよ
The first date is at a hotel.
初デートはホテルです
If it's cute, I get excited.
可愛いと、テンション上がっちゃうから
Are you nervous now?
今緊張してる?
why?
なんで?
What are you doing that makes you nervous?
どういうことするから緊張してるの?
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
Okay, I was drawn to it by gravity.
いいの、引力に惹かれましたね
This is how you normally hold it.
普通に持ってんじゃん、こうやって
I'm pulling this right now.
これ今、引いてるんですよ
Coo here.
こっちにクーって
Relax.
気抜く
I was just kidding.
ふざけたばっかり
I want to talk to you about various things.
いろいろお話しもしたくて
Is it okay if I ask?
聞いちゃっても大丈夫?
good
いい
is.
です
Now, I'm usually on line.
今、 普段ラインされてるの
Jedi.
ジェディー
Why is it so erotic when I say "Jeddy"?
なんで、こんなにも ジェディーって言うとエロくなるんだろう
hey.
ね
sorry.
ご めんなさい
ご め んなさい
A little erotic.
エロいとこちょっと
By the way, what school is that?
ちなみに、それは どこの学校か
The image is that people with a high level go there.
レ ベルの高い人が 行くっていうイメージ
In terms of looks.
ルックス的にね
It wasn't a microscope at first though.
最初は顕微じゃないけどね
He's smart and looks good too.
頭も良くて、 見た目も良いんだよ
I feel bad saying that.
言ってて悔しくなるんですけど
I'm a junior high school graduate.
僕、中卒なんで
No, no, no.
いやいやいや
It's a little awkward.
ちょっと、気まずくて
I can't say anything.
なんとも言えない
I'm good now.
今の俺がよく
What is the department?
学科とかなんなの?
The subject is economics.
学科は 経済
It doesn't suddenly disappear.
急に消えてない
Messed up.
めちゃくちゃ
This is an educational video.
これがね、 教育動画だから
That's it.
そっちのね
The education system there as well.
そっちの教育系もね
Completely naked.
全裸
That's nice.
いいですね
It's not shown on camera though.
カメラに映ってないけど
Is school fun?
学校楽しいですか?
It's fun.
楽しいです
What do today's students play?
今の学生、何して遊ぶの?
Friends and stuff.
友達とかと
A cafe or something.
カフェとか
A cafe?
カフェか
is that so.
そうですか
In between classes.
授業の合間とか
Do you even go there?
行 ったりもするの?
I do, but I always go to cute places on my days off.
もするんですけど、 やっぱり休みの日とかに 可愛いところ行
Something like that.
った りとか
Let's go, girls.
行くんだ、女の子たちって
Let's go, let's go.
行きます行きます
By the way, what are you doing now?
ちなみに今、 何ですか?
Do you have a part-time job?
バイトがされてるんですか?
I am doing.
してます
Chanso?
ちゃんそ?
Izakaya.
いざかや
Ah, what's going on?
あ、いざかやか
Izakaya.
いざかや
If I had a caregiver like this, I'd probably hold her hand if I was in Chanso.
こんな介護がいたら、ちゃんそにいたら 手繋いしちゃうね
So is Kokushi.
国司もそうだよ
Well then, Izakaya is Izakaya.
じゃあ、いざかやは、いざかやなんだ
It must be difficult, so do it.
大変でしょ、いざかやって
It's really difficult, isn't it?
めっちゃ大変ですよね
It's really difficult.
め っちゃ大変です
In places like Izakaya, they are still called customers.
いざかやとかで、やっぱりお客さんって呼ばれてるよね
yes.
はい
Are you not invited or not?
呼 ばれなかったりとかされない?
Or something like that.
声かけられたりなんか
I get involved sometimes.
たまに絡まれますね
You get involved, you know.
絡まれるよね、あったよね
It's like, let's have a drink with your sister.
お姉ちゃん一緒に飲もうよ、みたいなね
What will you do then?
その 時どうするの?
I've been working for a while.
ちょっと仕事してるんで
No, no, don't stop being stubborn.
いやいや、かたいことやめないでよ
Let's drink, let's drink.
飲もうよ、飲もうよって
I said I was going to get angry and ran away.
怒られちゃうねって言って、逃げました
Well then, you don't have to drink, just tell me about Lenas.
じゃあ、飲まなくていいから、 レナスだけ教えてよ
Sorry, I'm at work for a while.
ちょっと仕事中なんでごめんなさい、
Like.
みたいな
I don't have a smartphone.
スマホ持ってないんで
Well, I'll write this, then give me Lenas later.
じゃあ、俺これ書くから、 後でレナスちょうだいって
Can I just say I'm sorry?
ちょっと、ごめんなさいって言っていい?
At times like that?
そういう時?
Haven't you ever met a good person?
今までいい人いなかったの?
So.
それで
He wasn't there.
いなかったですね
Wasn't there?
いなかった?
I'm not there.
いないです
Am I the only one?
俺しかいない?
I stabbed it.
刺しました
Do you have a boyfriend?
彼氏はいるんですか?
I'm not there.
いないです
How long have you been gone?
どれくらいいないの?
About half a year.
半年くらい
Half a year?
半年?
I wrote it many times.
何度もかいちゃったんですよ
I was excited.
うわきされました
Are you excited?
うわきされたの?
I was excited.
うわきされました
How did that come about?
それはどうやって発覚したの?
Because of the boyfriend's line exchange, the other person also had a boyfriend.
彼氏の ラインの やりとりが だからその相手も 彼氏がいた
I found out about it when the boyfriend sent it to me.
んで その彼氏さんから送られてきて 知っちゃいました
Isn't it called Double Flynn?
ダブルフリンってやつじゃないの?
Well, that boyfriend was dating, and my own boyfriend was excited.
え、その彼氏が 彼氏が付き合って 自分の彼氏が うわきしてた
She also had a boyfriend, right?
女 にも彼氏いたんだよね?
that's right.
そうです
I often see it in manga, but it really does exist.
よく漫画に見るよ 本当にあるんだよ
actually?
実は?
Actually.
実はです
That's a little harsh.
それはちょっと きついね
It was really tough.
めちゃきつかったです
I'm not honest.
俺は素直しないよ
Is it true?
本当ですか?
That's nice.
いいですね
Your smile is cute.
笑顔がかわいいって
Is it true?
本当ですか?
By the way, oh, yes.
ちなみに あ、そうだ
You said Aoyama, but the rocks are so good, Miss Aoyama.
青山って言ってたんだけど こんなにロックスいいんで ミス青山
Did it feel right?
的 な 感じだったんすか?
Do you feel like you're looking a little higher?
もうちょっと上を見てる感じですか?
There is no sharing in the reservation specifications, so no, no, no.
予約の仕様には共有がないから いやいやいや、
Not at all.
まったく そんなことないです
You'll probably be told something like that, right? I guess it's good for the people around you, right?
なんか言われるでしょ 周りにも いけるんじゃない?
That's what you think too, right?
みたいな 自分でも思ってるでしょ?
No, not at all
いや、まったく
Well, it's really cute.
だ って、めっちゃかわいいよ
Even as proof of that
その証拠にだって
Because it's cute
か わいいから
Looks like a man's radar
男 のレーダーみたいだね
I was just glancing at you, are you curious?
ちょっと チラチラ見てたね 気になっちゃう?
Are you a little concerned?
ちょっと気になっちゃう?
He's so cute, he stands up just by talking, you know?
かわいいとさ 喋ってるだけで立っちゃうんだけど ほ ら、
Stand up, eh?
立って え?
The choices are A, B, and C, so A,
選択肢で ちゃんとA、B、Cで言うから A、
Since I make choices with B and C, what is the percentage of A?
B、Cで選択肢作るから Aの 割何?
Can I ask you to answer something like this?
みたいな 感じで答えてもらっていいですか?
Penis B
ちんこ B
Which one?
ど れでしょう?
Yes, please, please answer. B's Umaibo is good.
はい、お願いします 回答お願いします Bのうまい棒 いいっす
Hey, I thought you'd choose that one, but it's delicious.
ね それを選んでくれって 俺は思ってたんだけど うまい棒おい
I haven't eaten it because I don't want to eat it.
しい から食べちゃいない 食べちゃいない 言う食べちゃい
No, Umaibo
ない、 うまい棒
People don't usually do things like that, the first time they do it.
そんな ことされないよね 普段ね 初めてされば
I'm a little confused, but today I'll connect with you on SNS.
ちょっと どちらかっちゃったけど 今日は SNSの方で お連
Please contact me
絡 頂いて
I do this as a hobby, so I decided to take a picture of it this time.
は みどり趣味でやってるんで 今回撮らせて頂くと
Are you interested in such naughty things?
ちょっと そういうエッチなことには 興味あったりするの?
Yes Yes
あります ある
Good but
いい ですが
Today's phone call I heard you're my friend today's phone call.
今日 のテレフォン テレフォンで今日のお友達なんで 知ら
do not have?
ない?
Good, don't you know any friends?
いい 友知らない?
Got it? Got it?
分かりました 分かった?
You definitely got it, I get it.
絶対分かったでしょ 分かりますよ
What do you understand?
なんだ 分かった?
It's different
違いますよ
I felt a little depressed.
ちょっと しょんでなっちゃった
Are you supporting me?
応 援ですか?
Grow up
大きくなれって
So, are you cheering me on or telling me to grow up?
そう 応援っていうか 大きくなれって 口でですか?
It's so embarrassing.
ち んちんきょ 恥ずかしいの
Get bigger, get bigger
ち んちん大きくなれ 大きくなれ
Just a little bit
ちょっと ちょっと
I'm not in the mood at all
全 然ムードないんだけど
Any experience in front of the camera?
カ メラの前にある経験とか?
No. Do you feel nervous?
ない 緊張する?
I'm really nervous
めっちゃ緊張します
め っちゃ緊張します
The lipstick is soft. Is it soft?
口 紅柔らかいね 柔らかいですか?
It tasted like strawberries and was gross. Can I lick it?
いちごの味がした グロス感のし 舐めていい?
Are you going to lick it?
舐めるんですか?
I'm so nervous that I'm cute that I end up having trouble getting in the mood.
俺可愛いって緊張しすぎて 雰囲気つくのひたになっちゃうんだ
Is that so?
そう なんですか?
Sorry, but I just want to have some fun from now on.
ごめんね でもちょっと ここからは 楽しみたいっていうか
A lot, a lot
だ いぶ だいぶ
I'm going to take a naughty photo while making peace here, huh?
ここ でピースしながら エッチな撮影しますって え?
While peace
ピースしながら
I'm going to take a naughty photo from now on, sorry.
今 から エッチな撮影します す み ません
picture?
え?
Peace?
ピ ースですか?
peaced
ピースした
I made my choice while making the peace, but I was embarrassed to have to go there again.
ピ ースしながら チョイしたけど 恥ずかしい もう一回そこに
Take it out
下 出して
That umbrella
という かさ
What's this really sexy clothes?
め っちゃセクシーな服 何これ?
A-chan, can I touch you?
あちゃん、触っていいですか?
Clothes.
服をね
Clothes?
服を?
Can I touch your clothes?
服触っていい?
It's not clothes.
服じゃない
What do you mean?
どういうこと?
It's not clothes.
服じゃない
It's clothes.
服だよ
I'm touching my clothes now.
服触ってるよ、今
It feels good.
気持ちいいんだ
It smelled.
臭かったよ
It feels good here.
ここ気持ちいいんだ
Hey, okay.
ほら、いいよ
ほ ら、いいよ
Properly.
ちゃんと
picture?
え?
sorry.
ごめん
Did it smell?
臭かった?
It smelled.
臭かった
I'll stop walking.
足をやめるね
Touch it.
触るの
Oh, touch it.
え、 触るの
Until you put it in?
入れるまでですか?
Yes, I'll touch it.
うん、触るから
Say it while looking at the camera.
カメラ見ながら言って
picture?
え?
I feel like I want you to touch me a little.
ちょっと触ってほしいみたい
Huh?
あれ?
Right now, right now.
今、今ちょっと
I twitched though.
ピクッとなったけど
I thought it felt good.
気持ちいいとかとっちゃったよ
Well, I can't answer that at all.
じゃあ全然答えられないから
Is it a punishment game?
罰ゲームですか?
So, stand here.
じゃあ、ここ立って
Shall I take it off?
脱ごうか
picture?
え?
Are you going to take it off already?
もう脱ぐんですか?
Yeah.
うん
Hurry.
早っ
Should I take it off myself?
自分で脱ぐか
Hurry.
早っ
Surprised.
びっくり
That's good.
いい よな
Sorry.
ごめんね
Ah, yes.
あ、そう
I'm already in my underwear.
もう下着姿になって
picture?
え?
Here, here.
ここで、ここで
That's strange.
おかしいな
Because I want to see it already.
もう見たいからさ
So, can you say it?
じゃあ、言える?
This is because I couldn't answer the quiz earlier.
これ、さっきクイズに答えられなかったから
It's a punishment game, right?
罰ゲームですよね?
Yeah, you know, can you say that?
うん、あのね、言える?
Now then.
今じゃあ
Where did you touch me earlier?
さっきどこ触られてたの?
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
It's fine at your own timing.
自分のタイミングでいいよ
Take it off?
脱ぐ?
If you answer, uh...
答えてくれたら、あの...
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいね
So, can I take it off?
じゃあ、俺が脱がせる?
Is that better?
そっちのほうがいい?
I could see it a little.
ちょっと見えた
picture?
え?
But I can't see it yet.
でもまだ見えない
Can't you see?
見えない?
Turned over.
めくられた
Well then, okay.
じゃあ、いいよ
One more time.
もう一回さ
It's a bit embarrassing to take it off all of a sudden.
いきなり脱ぐのは、ちょっと恥ずかしいよね
So let's take a look first.
だからさっきにちょっと見ちゃおう
See, see.
見る、見る
Ah, I saw it.
あ、見えた
I let my guard down, so I saw it.
油断したから、見えた
a little bit.
ちょっと
picture?
え?
Nothing, nothing, nothing.
なんもない、なんもない、なんもない
Nothing?
なんもない?
Nothing, nothing.
なんもない、なんもない
Ah, okay.
あ、いいよ
So, keep your hands here.
じゃあ、手をここに置いといて
So, this is what it looks like.
で、姿この辺で
I can't see this.
これ、見えない
Because it doesn't look good.
いい感じに見えないから
Can't you see?
見えないですか?
Yeah, I can't see it at all.
うん、全然見えてない
Gen-chan.
ゲンちゃん
picture?
え?
Warm.
あったかい
Will you go to bed with me?
僕と一緒にベッドに行ってくれますか?
Shall we go?
行 く か?
I'm going.
行きます
Surprised.
びっくり
What are you doing?
何してんだろうって
But you know, I'm a little weird too.
でもね、俺ちょっと変なやつもあるから
Oh, something's on.
あ、なんかついてる
yes.
そう
Why don't you mess with this?
揉めないか、これじゃあ
After this is over, why don't we rub it together?
これが終わったら、揉めないか
strange?
おかしい?
strange.
おかしい
picture?
え?
Are you there?
いるの?
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
It's embarrassing.
恥 ず か しい
picture?
え?
Punishment game?
罰ゲーム?
Are you a good girl?
うまい子か
Punishment game?
罰ゲーム?
It's so beautiful.
めっちゃ綺麗じゃん
I'm purapura.
プラプラってしてる
high school student?
高校生?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Oh, it tickles.
あ、くすぐったい
Don't worry about it.
気にしないでいいか
Should I not worry about it?
気にしないでいいの?
When did you start wearing Brama?
ブラマいつからつけたの?
Oh, don't worry about saying it.
あ、言う気にしないでいいからね
Don't worry about it.
気 にしないでいい
No, no.
ダメ、ダメ
Is it okay to be ticklish?
くすぐったいのダメ?
No tickling.
くすぐったいのダメ
One more time, this time, it's all good.
もう一回さ、これでさ、グッとして
Do you like it?
グッてする?
Hold both knees.
両膝持って
I hope it doesn't tickle.
くすぐったいくなければいいんだよね
picture?
え?
What shall we do?
何をしよう?
Nothing.
何も
I won't do anything.
何もしないよ
Do nothing.
何もしない
what
何
Was it?
だ ったの?
There is.
あるんですって
It's my first time.
初めてですね
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
picture?
え?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
It's the scent of strawberries.
い ちごの香りだよ
It's a strawberry scent.
いちごの香りだよ
difficult.
難しい
Suddenly,
ワッキッと、
Lick it.
舐 めて
where?
どこ?
Lick my boobs.
おっぱい舐めて
Do you want me to lick you?
舐めてほしい?
Do you want me to lick your breasts?
お っぱい舐めてほしい?
I want you to lick me.
舐めてほしい
Oh, wait a minute.
や だ、ちょっと
No way.
やだ
I haven't taken any pictures anywhere.
どこも撮ってないよ
I'm taking pictures.
撮ってる
No way.
やだ
Oh no.
や だ
So, try a double piece.
それでさ、ダブルピースしてみて
Are you going to do a double piece?
ダブルピースするの?
I like Double Peace.
俺、好きなんだよ、ダブルピース
double piece.
ダブルピース
Please guide me on this point myself.
自分でさ、この点誘導して
Guide?
誘導する?
Well, since I couldn't read it again, then...
じゃあ、また読めなかったから、 じゃあ、
It's going to keep progressing.
どんどん進行していくよ
Will it progress?
進行していく?
Punishment.
罰が
Extra?
エクストロー?
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
Good.
よいしょ
No way.
やだ
Don't look.
見ないで
I don't see it, I don't see it, I don't see it.
見てない、見てない、見ない
Oh no.
や だ
I don't see it.
見ない
Okay, I won't watch it.
分かった、見ない
I don't see it.
見ない
Don't look.
見ないで
No way.
やだ
Oh yeah, stop it.
そうそう、やめて
Well then, let's watch it together.
じゃあ、一緒に見よう
Let's watch it together.
一緒に見ようよ
I don't see it.
見ない
I won't watch it.
見ないよ
Oh, sorry.
あー、ごめん
Can I see it?
見て いい?
You can look at it.
見ていいから
Can I see it?
見ていい?
It's good to see.
見ていいですよ
So beautiful.
めっちゃ綺麗
How does it feel to touch you?
どういう風に触るのが気持ちいいの?
Ah, this is it.
あ、これだ
Let's go, this is it.
いくよ、これなの
It's best to do it in a circular motion.
円描くようにやるのがいいんだ
Yeah.
うん
now.
今
This is cute.
これ可愛いね
Yeah yeah yeah.
うんうんうん
Mameyo.
まめよって
I might go.
いっちゃうかもしれないです
Wait, wait.
待って、待って
Did you just go?
今、いった?
I'm gone.
いっちゃった
Can you spread it out yourself?
自分でさ、広げて見せてくれる?
Well, from under your feet.
さ、足の下からさ
From below?
下 から?
do not have.
ない
where?
どこ?
here.
ここ
Greetrice.
グリートリス
Oh, it shook.
あ、揺れました
No, it's embarrassing.
やな、恥ずかしい
picture?
え?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
What to do?
何するところ?
There.
そこ
here?
ここ?
stomach
い
It happened.
っちゃ った
I'm going.
いっちゃう
terrible.
やばい
be on one's mind?
気になる?
Piss?
ピス?
Suck it out about the middle.
真ん中ぐらいに吸い出して
Will it end?
終わる?
Yeah.
うん
Very solid
すごい固
stomach.
い
It's already getting bigger.
もう 大きくなってる
Good stick.
うまい棒
You remembered it well.
よく覚えてたね
That's right, I forgot.
そうだ、俺が忘れてたんだ
Yes, it was a good stick.
そうだ、うまい棒だった
Good stick.
うまい棒
Eh, the water?
え、水の方?
What is it?
何だっけ?
Ching Chin.
チンチン
Over here?
こっちで?
Kocchi
こ っち
in.
で
What taste?
何 味?
What does it taste like?
何味?
Sweet
甘
stomach?
い?
sweet?
甘 い?
delicious?
おいしい?
delicious.
おいしい
So delicious.
チンチンおいしい
Mom, this.
お母さん、これ
I wanted to put it in.
入れたくなっちゃった
I can really fit it in.
め っちゃ入れるね
different.
違う
There aren't that many.
あんま無いよ
It's on.
ついてるよ
It's not on.
ついてない
It's on.
ついてるよ
It's not on.
ついてない
0.00...
Where?
どこで?
Ah, I thought I could go with the current flow.
あ、今の流れいけると思ってた
No.
ダメだよ
Look, look.
見て、ほら
It's on.
ついてるよ
It's not on.
ついてない
0.00...
It's not on.
ついてない
No?
ダメ?
It's not on.
ついてない
Let's do it live today.
今日生でしようよ
It's a little scary.
ちょっと怖い
This is kind, isn't it?
優しいでしょ、これ
You're kind, aren't you?
優しいでしょ
I'd be scared if I got pregnant.
妊娠とかしちゃったら怖いから
pregnancy?
妊娠?
You should just take it outside.
外に出せばいいじゃん
That's not the problem.
そういう問題じゃない
What kind of rubber?
何ゴムって
That's enough.
もういいから
It's okay, it's okay.
いいじゃん、いいじゃん
Just rub 3 times.
3回こするだけ
Just rub it 3 times?
3回こするだけ?
That's not the problem.
そういう問題じゃない
Try closing your eyes.
目閉じてみて
Close your eyes?
目閉じる?
Try closing your eyes.
目閉じてみて
Raise your feet.
足上げて
Do you raise your legs and close your eyes?
足上げて目閉じるの?
Close your eyes and feel normal.
目閉じてみて、普通に
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
picture?
え?
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
That's enough.
もういいじゃん
Let's just put it in a little bit.
ちょっとだけ入れようよ
Just a little, just a little.
ちょっとだけ、ちょっとだけ
No, no, no.
ダメ、ダメ、ダメ
Not just a little bit.
ちょっとだけじゃない
Just a little bit.
ちょっとだけ
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Place your right hand slightly behind your back
右側の手を少し後ろにして
please.
ください
Completely remove the upper body all the way to the back.
後 ろ側まで上半身だけ完全に取
I will.
ります
Bring your hands slightly forward.
手 を少し前にしてください
Let's try it again.
もう 一度やってみましょう
Put your hands down a little.
手を少し下にしてください
Bring your hands a little forward.
手を少し前にしてください
I'd like to use it not only for pets, but also for other things.
ペットだけじゃなくてさ、他のところも使ってみたいんだけどさ
Okay.
いいよ
It feels so good, because of that,
気持ち良すぎてさ、あれだからさ、
It's cool time.
クールタイムです
Just a little check.
ちょっとチェックメントで
Checkment?
チェックメント?
yes?
そう?
Checkment?
チェックメント?
Come
来
If so, I wanted it.
そうだ ったら欲しかった
Senmen line
せんめんラインを
do.
する
Let's stand back here.
立 ちバックしようよ、ここで
Here?
ここで?
Yes, then push up and move backwards.
そう、じゃあ押し上げついて、後ろに
Another one
もう一
degree.
度
once again.
もう 一度
Looks like I'm about to go.
そろそろ行きそう
What should I do?
どうしていい?
Outside.
外ね
Looks like I'm going.
行きそう
what?
何?
Something about both knees.
何か両膝
Looks like it was out.
出ちゃってたっぽい
picture?
え?
Take some.
ちょっと取ってよ
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
No, but...
いや、でも...
You said it at such a wrong time.
あんな間違いのタイミングで言われてんのに
Oh, because...
え、だって...
If it's a season...
シーズンとかしたら...
Ah, but then...
あ、でも、そしたら...
Then it would be dangerous...
そしたら危ないから...
Write it down.
書き出す
I'll write it down once and for all.
書き出すわ、いったん
Write it down?
書き出す?
Look, I've been staring at you now.
見て、今見つめてきたから
It's okay because I wrote it down.
書き出したから大丈夫だよ
Because it's not in there anymore.
もう入ってないから
Is there such a thing?
そんなことある?
Are you okay.
大丈夫
Because it's not in there anymore.
もう入ってないから
I wrote it down, but if you're worried,
一応書き出したけど、 もし不安だったら、
It's better to keep your mouth and mouth still.
下 も口も静止入れたほうがいいから
Are the bottom and mouth still?
下も口も静止?
What do you mean?
どういうこと?
It's better to keep the upper mouth still.
上の口も静止入れたほうがいいから
Do you do everything?
全部するの?
Yeah.
うん
It's okay now.
これでもう大丈夫だ
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Is this okay?
これで大丈夫?
It's okay now.
これでもう大丈夫だ
It's okay, but I thought I'd like to ask you something.
大丈夫だけど、 一応聞いておきたいなと思って、
For future reference.
今後の参考に
how was it?
どうだった?
in the first place.
そもそも
It's dangerous though.
危ないけど
It felt good.
気持ちよかった
Did it feel good?
気持ちよかった?
It felt good.
気持ちよかった
That's what I said.
言ってたもん
For the first time, I felt like my spirit was standing inside.
初めて、 中で精神って立ってた感じ、
how was it?
どうだった?
It's like, you're guessing.
当ててるな、みたいな
I feel like my heart is pounding.
ドクドクしてるな、みたいな
It's probably okay, and I'll do something about it.
多分大丈夫だし、俺も何とかするから
But just for once, I want to talk about a lot of things.
でも一回ちょっとさ、 いろいろ話したいし、
This will happen again, so I'll contact you again soon.
またこのこともあるし、 またちょっと連絡するからさ、
In the recent past.
直近で
Well then, please try talking to me again.
じゃあ、もう一回話してみてちゃんと
Well, this time I'll end with a little piece and a double piece.
じゃあ、今回ちょっとピースで、 ダブルピースで終わり
Let's.
ましょう
Creampie sex felt good,
中 出しエッチ、気持ちよかったって、
Shall I say it?
言ってみようか
Creampie sex felt so good.
中出しエッチ、気持ちよかった